mobstac.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy policy - Beaconstac

### Introduction:

This Privacy Policy was last updated on July 20th 2018 

At MobileMotion Technologies we understand the care you assign towards usage and sharing of your information and we appreciate your unwavering trust that we will do so carefully. This notice describes our privacy policy.

MobStac Inc. a Delaware incorporated entity is a fully owned subsidiary of MobileMotion Technologies Private Limited (hereinafter collectively referred to as “MobStac”, “We”, “Us” or “Our”). This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, and disclose information when you visit or use our websites [www.mobstac.com](https://www.mobstac.com/) or www.beaconstac.com or [https://eddy.pro ](https://eddy.pro/) (hereinafter collectively referred to as “Site”) or any of the **“Service(s)”** provided by Us. Any capitalised terms not defined here have meanings set out in our Terms of Use. 

This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by us when you access the Service(s), how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not knowingly use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. The use of information collected through our Site shall be limited to the purposes under this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service and Terms of Sale. 

By visiting this Site or providing your personal information to one of our sales representatives or live chat representatives or signing up or logging in you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy. Please note that this includes consenting to the processing of any sensitive personal information you provide, as described below. 

Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. By using our Services, you consent to the use and sharing of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE PRACTICES, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SERVICES, OR OTHERWISE PROVIDE US WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. 

For the purpose of the European Parliament and the Council’s Regulation 2016/679 of 27 April 2016 (“GDPR”); the Data Controller is MobileMotion Technologies having address at 316, 100 feet road, Indiranagar, Bangalore, INDIA 560038 

### Some key terms

In our Privacy Policy:

  * **“Customers”** (hereinafter collectively referred to as “You”, “Your”, “User”), mean our customers who use our Service(s) 
  * “Service(s)” include without limitation the Beaconstac software and hardware or visiting or using our site or any new site, software, hardware, which we may introduce. 
  * **“Service Data”** means all electronic data, text, messages or other materials, including Personal Data of Users, submitted to the Service(s) by You in connection with Your use of the Service(s), including, without limitation, to Personal Data. 
  * **“Personal Data”** means data relating to a living individual who is or can be identified either from the data or from the data in conjunction with other information that is in, or is likely to come into, the possession of the data controller (as defined under Applicable Data Protection Law). 
  * **“Applicable Data Protection Law”** means EU Regulation 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation) and where You are established in any other territory, means data protection laws that are applicable in that territory. 

### Scope:

This policy covers the below mentioned:

  * What personal information about Customers does MobStac collect?
  * Use of Information
  * Cookies and Similar Technologies
  * Sharing of Information
  * Transfer of Personal Information
  * Security of your information
  * Advertising and links to other sites
  * What rights you have?
  * Privacy of Children
  * California Do Not Track
  * Questions/Changes to policy

### What personal information about Customers does MobStac collect?

The information we learn from customers can be broadly classified into three categories as mentioned below, such information helps us personalize and continually improve our services and hence your experience: 

#### Information you provide us:

We receive and store any information you enter on our site or give us in any other way. For example, during sign up you provide us with name, email, address, telephone and your credit card details. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of all of our services and features. We use the information that you provide for purposes such as responding to your requests, shipping the beacons to your respective locations, to convey across any promotional offers from us or the third parties we work with and communicating with you. 

By providing us with this information, you expressly consent to our use of your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

#### Information we collect automatically:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our Site or advertisements served by or on behalf of MobStac on other sites. 

We collect navigational information about what Site pages you access or visit, your device’s Internet Protocol “IP” address, information about your mobile device (such as operating system of your mobile device or browser type), the URLs of websites that referred you to us, non-precise geographic location, technical information about your device, data about the type of browser and operating system used, which web pages you view, the time and duration or you visits to our Site, the search queries you may use on the Site, whether you clicked on any advertisements, whether you have clicked on any links in any e-mails sent from us, or third-parties on our behalf and whether you have chosen to opt-out of certain services or information sharing and other metadata concerning with your usage of our Services. 

#### Information from Other Sources:

Our Site may include buttons, tools, or information that link to other third-party services (for example, a Facebook "Comment" button). We may collect information about your use of these features. In addition, when you see or interact with these buttons, tools, or information, or view a MobStac web page containing them, some information from your browser may automatically be sent to the other company. Please read that company’s privacy policy for more information. You can refer to the list of third parties . 

### Use of Information

We may use your personal information including but not limited to the following purposes: 

  * To administer your use of our Services 
  * To better understand your needs and interests 
  * To better understand and improvise our products and services 
  * To facilitate your use and personalizing your experience on the Site 
  * To serve you relevant ads 
  * To respond to your inquiries or fulfilling your requests for information about our Service(s) 
  * To provide you with information about our Services and sending you information and materials from MobStac including marketing communication 
  * To help you address problems with the Site, including any technical problems 
  * To Process online job application, you might have applied for 
  * To detect and prevent identity theft, fraud, and other potentially illegal acts as well as protecting the integrity of the website 
  * To respond to subpoenas, court orders, or judicial processes 
  * To provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety 
  * To resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems 
  * To help with any investigations or complaints 
  * To provide you with relevant information or Service(s) that you request from us or which we feel may interest you based on previous interactions, where you have consented to be contacted 

### How we use Cookies and Similar Technologies?

Cookies are bits of electronic information that a website may transfer to a visitor's computer to identify specific information about the visitor's visits to a website. The Site uses a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer, in case you do not wish us to collect such information kindly refer to our cookie policy. You can access the details of our Cookie Policy here. 

If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that store cookies. 

Alternatively, you may wish to visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) which contains comprehensive information on how to manage cookies on a wide variety of browsers. However, please note that if you disable the use of cookies on your computer, some functionalities of our Services will not work. 

### Sharing of Information

MobStac provides your personal information to third parties who are obligated to use the personal information that we share with them for the purpose of provision of their services to us in order to help us run our business. These third parties include but are not limited to business partners, suppliers, sub-contractors, advertisers & advertising networks, analytics & search engine providers, payment providers. We may also share with third parties aggregate information or information that does not personally identify you. Should you require more details on third parties we work with or have any questions around it, please click here to know more about the third parties we work with. 

For example, we use Stripe to manage our payments, but we reserve the right to change this service provider at any time for any reason. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards. Your credit card information will also be subject to our payment processor’s privacy policy in addition to ours. PLEASE READ THE PRIVACY POLICY ON THE WEBSITE OF ANY PAYMENT PROCESSOR THAT YOU ARE DIRECTED TO REGARDING THE USE, STORAGE AND PROTECTION OF YOUR CREDIT CARD INFORMATION BEFORE SUBMITTING ANY CREDIT CARD INFORMATION. When you make a charge, we shall display a completed charge screen. This is your electronic receipt. You should print or save this electronic receipt for your records. YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE THE LEGAL RIGHT TO USE ANY CREDIT CARDS, DEBIT CARDS OR OTHER PAYMENT MEANS USED TO INITIATE ANY TRANSACTION. 

We may also share your personal information in the following circumstances 

  * When we are required to provide information in response to a subpoena, court order, or other applicable law or legal process. 
  * When we have a good faith belief that the disclosure is necessary to prevent or respond to fraud, defend our apps or websites against attacks, or protect the property and safety of MobStac, our customers and users, or the public. 
  * If we merge with or are acquired by another company, sell a MobStac website, app, or business unit, or if all or a substantial portion of our assets are acquired by another company. In those cases, your information will likely be one of the assets that is transferred. 

There are several places within the Site and our App that allow you to post comments or submit Service Data for others to see. Any information you choose to provide should reflect how much you want others to know about you. Please consider carefully what information you disclose in your profile page. You can review and revise your profile information at any time. To remove Service Data, you have shared on the Site or our App, you may use the same features (available on the Site) to do so. In case you have any query regarding removal and or deletion of such contact you can write to us at [legal@mobstac.com](mailto:legal@mobstac.com)

### Storage and Transfer of Personal Information

Your Personal Data and files are stored on MobStac’s servers and the servers of companies we hire to provide services to us. Your personal information may be transferred across national borders because we have servers located in United states, and the companies we hire to help us run our business may be located in different countries around the world. 

The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored in, a country outside the European Economic Area (EEA). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. The laws in some countries may not provide as much legal protection for your information as in the EEA. By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. 

### Security of your information

We understand that the security of your personal information is important. We provide reasonable administrative, technical, and physical security controls to protect your personal information. At the same time, it is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. However, despite our efforts, no security controls are 100% effective and MobStac cannot ensure or warrant the security of your personal information.

### Advertising and links to other sites

We might display interest-based advertising on both our sites and unaffiliated sites using information you make available to us when you interact with our site or Service(s). Interest-based ads, also sometimes referred to as personalized or targeted ads, are displayed to you based on information from activities including but not limited to usage of our Service(s) and visiting sites that contain MobStac content or ads. 

We use cookies, web beacons and other technologies (collectively, “cookies and similar technologies”). Cookies enable us to learn about what ads you see, what ads you click, and other actions you take on our sites and other sites. This allows us to provide you with more useful and relevant ads. For example, by knowing what ads you are shown we can be careful not to show you the same ones repeatedly. For more information about the use of cookies and similar technologies for interest-based advertising, please refer to our cookie policy here. 

Some of the functionality on our Service(s) may be provided by third parties that are not affiliated with MobStac. These entities may collect or receive certain information about your use of our Service(s) and your activities over time and across different websites, including through the use of cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, third-party cookies, web beacons, or other tracking technologies. MobStac is not responsible for the privacy practices of these entities. In addition, our Service(s) may contain links to other websites not operated or controlled by us. Such websites are not under our control and we are not responsible for their privacy policies or practices. If you provide any personal information through any such third-party website, we recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policies and practices of that third party. 

You may choose to enable or log in to our Service(s) via various online services like Google, including social networking services like Facebook, LinkedIn etcetera. Our services also may enable you to access social networking services such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, or Google (collectively, “Social Network”) directly or indirectly through our Services. 

When you link a Social Network account to our App or log into our Service(s) using your Social Network account, we may collect relevant information necessary to enable our Service(s) to access that Social Network and your data contained within that Social Network. We may share your information with the operator of that Social Network to facilitate or enhance delivery of that Social Network or other Service(s) to you. A Social Network may provide us with access to certain information that you have provided to them, and we will use, store, and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Additionally, a Social Network may collect personal information and information about your use of our Site or Service(s) automatically. The manner in which a Social Network collects, uses, stores, and discloses your information is governed by the policies of such third parties and MobStac shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Social Network that may be enabled within its Service(s). 

### What rights you have?

#### Right to be informed:

You are entitled to know whether we hold your personal information and the purpose your personal data is processed for. For more information regarding how long we retain your data please feel free to reach out to us at [legal@mobstac.com](mailto:legal@mobstac.com). 

####  Right of access: 

You are entitled to know the categories of your personal data being processed, the purposes of such processing, and the details of third parties to whom the data may have been disclosed. For more details please refer to the list of third parties here. 

####  Right to rectification: 

You are entitled to correct / update your personal information available with us. 

####  Right to erasure: 

You are entitled to get your data erased from our databases. Please note that we might need to retain certain information about you for reasons including but not limited to legal, internal business and fraud prevention. We will retain your personal information for as long as necessary to provide you with the services you are eligible to use and as needed to comply with our legal obligations and enforce our agreements. 

#### Right to data portability:

You have a right to object / restrict the processing of your data in some circumstances, including where the data is inaccurate (for the period during which we are verifying the data), the data is no longer required in light of the purpose of processing, or in connection with direct marketing (you can prevent / discontinue marketing communications to you by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your personal data), or by utilizing opt-out mechanisms in the emails we send you. 

In the above cases, we will retain minimum personal data to note that you opted out from being contacted again. For raising requests pertaining to the above-mentioned rights, please write to us at [legal@mobstac.com](mailto:legal@mobtac.com) . Please note some of the rights mentioned herein may not be available as we are designing the technical capabilities to comply with such requests; having said the above MobStac will do its best to resolve your request to the best of its ability. 

### Privacy of Children

We recognize the importance of children's safety and privacy. We do not request, or knowingly collect, any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18. MobStac is very sensitive to privacy issues regarding children. By visiting this Site or providing your personal information to one of our call-centre operators or live chat representatives or starting your free trial or signing up or logging in you are claiming yourself to be 18 years of age or above. 

If you believe that any child under the age of 18 has posted any personal information anywhere on our website, please contact us immediately at [legal@mobstac.com](mailto:legal@mobstac.com) and provide as much information as you can to help us locate and delete the personal information. 

If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child or any other child under the age of 18 has provided us with personal information, he or she should write to us at [legal@mobstac.com](mailto:legal@mobstac.com)

### California Do Not Track

MobStac does not have a mechanism in place for responding to browser “do not track” signals or other similar mechanisms used to limit collection of information for use in Online Behavioural Advertising. There currently is no consensus among industry participants as to what "Do Not Track" means in this context. Therefore, like many websites and online services, the Services do not alter their practices when they receive a "Do Not Track" signal from a visitor's browser. To find out more about "Do Not Track," please visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/). 

### Questions/Changes to policy

MobStac welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that we have not adhered to this Policy or If you have questions or concerns with respect to our Privacy Policy, please write to us at [legal@mobstac.com](mailto:legal@mobstac.com).
